





#### Summary

Jump to Section

Result-oriented Professional with over 5 years of experience in Software Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Product Development, Software Testing, Unit Testing, Bug Tracking, Core Java, J2Ee, HTML, SQL, Spring Boot, M.C. Edipse, Scrum.

Capabilities in working with senior management for integrating human resource functions with overall Business Goals and Industry Standards and balancing needs of employees & missions of the organization.

### **Work Experience**

ciel as Senior Software Engineer May 2020 to Till Date

I am a java backend developer

Datamatics Global services Ltd. as System Software Engineer Aug 2018 to Mar 2020

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

HP India Software Operations Pvt Ltd. as Software Engineer Dec 2017 to Aug 2018

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Bectronics/Telecommunication) from krupajal engineering college, Orissa. in 2014

^ Back to Top

## IT Skills

| Skill Name      | Version Last Used Experience |
|-----------------|------------------------------|
| JAVA,J2EE       |                              |
| HTML ,Tomcat    |                              |
| Oracle, Eclipse |                              |
| WINDOWS         |                              |

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld SVN, Perforce, GIT

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| Hindi    |             |      |       |       |
| English  |             |      |       |       |
| Oriya    |             |      |       |       |

^ Back to Top

**Affirmative Action** 

**Work Authorization** 

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.